Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- C
  - Correspondance socialiste internationale Place of publication: Paris, France, 1955-1959 (Box 70, 115)
  - Correspondence of the Young International Place of publication: Berlin, Germany Publisher: Executive Committee of the Communist Young International, 1922 (Box 111)
  - Counter-Attack Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee Against Academic Repression, 1969 (Box 115)
  - Counterattack: The Newsletter of Refuse & Resist! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Refuse & Resist!, 1987-1997 (Box 114)
  - CPSB Newsletter Place of publication: Birmingham, Ala. Publisher: Committee for Prisoner Support in Birmingham, 1975 (Box 341)
  - Crazy Horse Spirit Place of publication: Rapid City, So. Dekota Publisher: Leonard Peltier Defense Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 115A)
  - Crisis Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Socialist Labor Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 115)
  - Critical Mass Journal Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Critical Mass Energy Project, 1978-1979 (Box 115)
  - Crossbronx Express Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Bronx Coalition, 1970 (Box 115)
  - CRV/NY Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee of Returned Volunteers, nd (Box 115)
  - Crystal City News Place of publication: Bowling Green, Ohio, 1971 (Box 115)
  - CSA Contract Update Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Council of Supervisors and Administrators, Local 1, American Federation of School Administrations, AFL-CIO, 1998-1999 (Box 116A)
  - CSA News Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Council of Supervisors and Administrators, Local 1, American Federation of School Administrations, AFL-CIO, 2005-current (Box 116A)
  - CSTG Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Civil Service Technical Guild Local 375, 1979-1980 (Box 115)
  - Cuba: revista menusal Place of publication: Havana, Cuba, 1968 (Box 115A)
  - Cuba internacional Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Agencia Prensa Latina, 1974-1977 (Box 115A-115B)
  - Currents Place of publication: Des Moines, Iowa Publisher: Citizens United for Responsible Energy, 1981 (Box 115A)
  - CWA News Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, 1953-current (Box 71-73)
  - CWA State Worker Place of publication: Newark, N.J. Publisher: CWA New Jersey State Worker Locals, 1987 (Box 115)
- D
  - D.C. Free Press Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: D.C. Independent Media Center, 2001-2002 (Box 117)
  - D.C. Newsletter / Painters District Council 9 of New York City Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Painters District Council 9, 1967-1972 (Box 316)
  - Daily Challenge Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Thomas H. Watkins, 1975 (Box 117)
  - Daily Compass Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: T.O. Thackery, 1952 (Box 117)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7026)
  - Daily Planet Place of publication: Miami, Fla., 1969-1972 (Box 115)
  - Daily World Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Long View Pub. Co., 1968 (Box 116)
  - Dandelion: Newsletter of the Movement for a New Society Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Movement for a New Society, 1980-1983 (Box 115)
  - Dawn Place of publication: Manchester, England Publisher: Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers, 1973-1989 (Box 115-116)
  - DC 1707 Voice: Official Publication of District Council 1707, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: District Council 1707, Community & Social Agency Employees Union, 1986-2005 (Box 115)
  - Defender Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Sailors Union of the Pacific, Seattle Branch, 1949-1950 (Box 117)
  - Defenestrator Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 2001-2002 (Box 115)
  - Democratic Socialism Place of publication: Kingston, Jamaica Publisher: Agency for Public Information, 1976 (Box 117)
  - Demokratia Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Anti-Dictatorial Committee of Greeks and Americans for Democracy, 1968-1973 (Box 117)
  - Derelicked Place of publication: U.S.A., 1970 (Box 117)
  - Destroyer Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Resistance, 1970 (Box 162)
  - Det Nye Arbejderblad, 1947-1953 (Box 435)
  - Detroit Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Detroit Free Press, 1983 (Box 117)
  - Detroit Teacher Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Detroit Federation of Teachers, 1970 (Box 117)
  - Dialog Pre-Convention Discussion Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: CPUSA, 1991 (Box 117)
  - Different Drummer Place of publication: Little Rock, Ark., 1970 (Box 117)
  - Direct Action Place of publication: Bellingen, Australia Publisher: Australian Industrial Workers of the World, 2001-2002 (Box 117)
  - Dispatcher Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: International Longshore and Warehousemen's Union, 1969-current (Box 118-120)
  - Distant Drummer Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 1967-1970 (Box 120)
  - Distributive Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Distributive Workers of America, 1969-1990 (Box 121)
  - District 2 Marine Engineer Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: District 2, Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO, 1961-1970 (Box 122)
  - District Council 9 News / Painters District Council 9 of New York City Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Painters District Council 9, 1957-1966 (Box 316)
  - District Three Leader / International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers Place of publication: East Rutherford, N.J. Publisher: District Three Union IUE-AFL-CIO, 1978-1988 (Box 122)
  - Do It NOW Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National NOW Action Center, 1974-1977 (Box 123)
  - Dock of the Bay Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1969 (Box 123)
  - Dockers News / Written and Edited by Members of the I.L.A. Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Members of the International Longshoremen's Association, 1951-1986 (Box 120)
  - Door Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1971-1972 (Box 123)
  - Dressmakers' Voice: Central Organ of the Dressmakers Left-Wing Opposition of the I.L.G.W.U. Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Left wing Local 22, ILGWU, 1934 (Box 117)
  - Druid Free Press Place of publication: Tucson, Ariz. Publisher: Druid Free Press, 1970 (Box 123)
  - Drunken Boat Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Drunken Boat, 1993 (Box 120)
  - Duck Power Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: GI's Against Fascism, 1969 (Box 162)
  - Dynamic! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Communist League of the U.S.A., 1984-2001 (Box 123)
- E
  - The Eagle Eye Place of publication: Huntsville, Ala. Publisher: National Democratic Party of Alabama, 1970 (Box 123)
  - Eastern Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Eastern Conference of Service Employees Unions, 1967-1974 (Box 123)
  - Eat the State!: A Forum for Anti-authoritarian Political Opinion, Research, and Humor Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Eat the State, 2004-current (Box 123A)
  - Economic Democrat: A Publication of the Campaign for Economic Democracy Place of publication: Santa Monica, Calif. Publisher: Campaign for Economic Democracy, 1981-1982 (Box 128)
  - Edge City Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y., 1970 (Box 123)
  - Educational Notes Publisher: International Socialists, 1976 (Box 123)
  - El Foro del Pueblo Place of publication: Los Angeles, CA. Publisher: Editorial Prensa Sembradora, 1980-1981 (Box 123A)
  - El Salvador's Link Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Casa El Salvador Farabundo Martí, 1984-1987 (Box 128)
  - Electrical Union World: Official Organ of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-current (Box 124-127A)
  - The Elements Place of publication: Washington, D.C., 1975-1978 (Box 128)
  - Empire State Teacher Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y. Publisher: Empire State Federation of Teachers, AFT, 1957-1965 (Box 127A)
  - Energy News Digest Place of publication: Allendale, N.J. Publisher: Citizens Energy Council, 1981 (Box 128)
  - Enlisted Times Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Military Studies Center, 1977 (Box 128)
  - Enrage Place of publication: U.S.A., 1969 (Box 281)
  - L'Enrage Place of publication: Paris, France, 1968 (Box 128)
  - Eolas / Irish Republican Movement Place of publication: Dublin, Ireland Publisher: Irish Republican Movement, 1978 (Box 128)
  - Equal Times Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Eunice West, 1977-1979 (Box 128A)
  - Equity News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Actor's Equity Association, 1982-current (Box 129-129A)
  - Ergo Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Ergo, 1972 (Box 128)
  - España libre: organo del Comité Antifascista Español de los Estados Unidos Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Comité Antifascista Español de los Estados Unidos, 1940-1977 (Box 123A)
  - Espoir Place of publication: Toulouse, France Publisher: Unions Regionales de la C.N.T.F., 1973-1982 (Box 27)
  - L'Étudiant révolutionnaire: organe de la Fédération des Étudiants Révolutionnaires Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Fédération des Étudiants Révolutionnaires, 1968 (Box 130)
  - Eulenspiegel Place of publication: Berlin, Germany Publisher: Eulenspiegel-Verlagsgesellschaft, 1931 (Box 128)
  - Every GI Is a P.O.W. Place of publication: Monterey, Calif. Publisher: GI's from Fort Ord, 1972 (Box 162)
  - Everything for Everybody Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Everything for Everybody, 1975-1977 (Box 128)
  - Everywoman Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif., 1970-1972 (Box 130)
  - Exagéré: archives de l'avenir Place of publication: Paris, France, 1987-1988 (Box 128)
  - Exit Nine Place of publication: New Brunswick, N.J., 1973 (Box 130)
  - Eye Place of publication: Gainesville, Fla., 1971 (Box 130)
- F
  - Fag Rag Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Fag Rag Inc., nd (Box 165)
  - Fair Measure: Newsletter of Southerners for Economic Justice Place of publication: Greenville, S.C. Publisher: Southerners for Economic Justice, 1978-1984 (Box 134)
  - The Faith Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Black Allied Student Association, NYU, 1968 (Box 134)
  - Falcemartello Place of publication: Florence, Italy, 1968 (Box 134)
  - Falling Apart Place of publication: U.S.A., nd (Box 134)
  - Farah Strike News Place of publication: U.S.A., 1972 (Box 134)
  - Fateh Place of publication: Beirut/Montreal Publisher: Palestine National Liberation Movement, 1970-1971 (Box 319)
  - Fatigue Press Place of publication: Austin, Tex. Publisher: Ft. Hood GI's, 1969?-1971 (Box 162)
  - Fault Lines Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: SF Bay Area Independent Media Center, 2004 (Box 162)
  - Fed Up! Place of publication: Tacoma, Wash., 1970-1973 (Box 162)
  - Fedders Strike Support News Place of publication: New Brunswick, N.J. Publisher: All You Can Eat Collective, 1972 (Box 134)
  - La Federacion Obrera Puertorriquena Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Lords Party, 1972 (Box 134)
  - Federation News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Federation of Labor and Industrial Union Council, 1976-1996 (Box 131-133)
  - The Federation Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York State AFL-CIO, 1978-1983 (Box 134)
  - Federation Voice Place of publication: Maumee, Ohio Publisher: Federation of Long Lines Telephone Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 134)
  - FedNews Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: National Association of Government Employees, 1982-2001 (Box 135)
  - The Felon Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Irish-American Action Association, 1969 (Box 134)
  - Feminist Art Journal Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Feminist Art Journal, Inc., 1972-1977 (Box 135)
  - Feminist Bulletin Place of publication: Scarborough, N.Y. Publisher: Feminist Bulletin, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 130)
  - Feminist Communications Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: Feminist Communications, 1978 (Box 134)
  - The Feminist Voice Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: The Feminist Voice, 1971 (Box 477)
  - Festival Place of publication: Vienna, Austria Publisher: International Preparatory Committee for the 7th World Festival of Youth and Students for Peace and Friendship, 1958 (Box 135)
  - Festival informa Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: XI Festival Mundial de la Juventud y los Estudiantes, Comisión Permanente del Comité Internacional Preparatorio, 1978 (Box 136)
  - Fifth Estate Place of publication: Detroit, Mich., 1976-2000 (Box 135-136)
  - The Fifth Wheel Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Bay Area Teamster United Rank and File, 1971-1978 (Box 135)
  - Fight Against War and Fascism Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American League Against War and Fascism, 1933-1937 (Box 137-138)
  - Fight Back!: Monthly Newspaper of the Revolutionary Student Brigade Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1974-1977 (Box 162)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7736)
  - Fight Back!: News and Views from the People's Struggle Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: Fight Back!, 2001-2007 (Box 135)
  - Fight for Peace and Democracy Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Executive Committee of the American League Against War and Fascism, 1938-1939 (Box 138)
  - Fight to Win Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Worker-Student Alliance (SDS), nd (Box 139)
  - Fighting Back Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: All-People's Congress, People's Anti-War Mobilization, Students and Youth Against Racism, 1985-1990 (Box 139)
  - Fighting Back Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Youth Against War & Fascism, 1970 (Box 134)
  - Fighting Worker: Publication of the Revolutionary Workers Group Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Group, 1983 (Box 134)
  - Final Warning Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Final Warning, 1972-1975 (Box 134)
  - Fire Lines Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Uniformed Firefighters Association, 1971-1986 (Box 139)
  - Fire Next Time Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago SDS, 1969? (Box 139)
  - Fire! Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: SDS, 1969 (Box 139)
  - Firing Line Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Joint Community Union and National Organizing Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 139)
  - Fish Cheer, 1971 (Box 178)
  - Flecha Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: International Committee Against Racism, 1980-1984 (Box 31)
  - Focal Point Place of publication: Santa Monica, Calif. Publisher: Indochina Peace Campaign, 1973-1975 (Box 139)
  - Focus: Auto Workers Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Black Panther Caucus, 1970 (Box 357)
  - Focus: Communist Party Weekly Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Focus, 1985 (Box 139)
  - For Peace & Solidarity Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Solidarity Project, 1985-1987 (Box 139)
  - For the People Place of publication: New Bedford, Mass., 1977-1981 (Box 130)
  - Force Ouvrière Hebdo Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: CGT-FO, 1982-current (Box 139-149E)
  - Forefront Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees Union, 1974-1976 (Box 139)
  - Forty Acres and a Mule Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Educational Program of the New York Urban League, 1968-nd (Box 151)
  - Fourth World Place of publication: Downview, Ontario Publisher: Masada, 1971 (Box 487)
  - Foward Motion Place of publication: Storrs, Conn. Publisher: Coalition, 1974 (Box 151)
  - A Four-Year Bummer Place of publication: Champaign, Ill., 1969?-1971 (Box 162)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7324)
  - The Fourth International Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Organization of Executive Committee of Fourth International, 1968-1969 (Box 151)
  - Fourth World Place of publication: Downsview, Ontar. Publisher: Masada, 1971 (Box 487)
  - The Fourth World Place of publication: Oakland, Calif., 1971? (Box 477)
  - Fox Valley Kaleidescope Place of publication: Oshkosh, 1970 (Box 151)
  - Fragging Action Place of publication: Cookeytown, N.J. Publisher: GI's of Fort Dix, 1971-1972 (Box 162)
  - Free Angela: Newsletter of the San Francisco Committee to Free Angela Davis and the National United Committee to Free Angela Davis Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1971 (Box 152)
  - Free Campus News Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Young Americans for Freedom (Box 151)
  - Free Enterprise Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: We, The People, 1961-1963 (Box 151)
  - Free Flowing Place of publication: Ames, Iowa, 1976 (Box 151)
  - Free for All Place of publication: Madison, Wis., 1973-1981 (Box 150)
  - Free Labour World Place of publication: Belgium Publisher: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1985-1997 (Box 151)
  - Free Palestine Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Friends of Free Palestine, 1968-1972 (Box 319)
  - Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Free People's Movement, 2007 (Box 162)
  - Free Press of Louisville Place of publication: Louisville, Ky., nd (Box 152)
  - Free Press Underground Place of publication: Columbia, Mo. Publisher: Columbia Free Press Corp., 1967 (Box 152)
  - Free Ranger Intertribal News Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Free Ranger Tribe and Underground Press Syndicate, 1970-1971 (Box 152)
  - Free Student Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: May 2nd Movement, 1965 (Box 152)
  - The Free Venice Beachhead Place of publication: Venice, Calif., 1968-1974 (Box 152)
  - Free Vermont Place of publication: Putney, Vt. Publisher: Red Clover Collective, nd (Box 152)
  - Free You Place of publication: Menlo Park, Calif. Publisher: Midpeninsula Free University, 1970 (Box 152)
  - Freedom Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga., 1963-1964 (Box 152)
  - Freedom: The Anarchist Weekly Place of publication: London, England, 1983-2007 (Box 154-156A)
  - Freedom Anarchist Weekly Place of publication: London, England, 1964-1975 (Box 153-154)
  - Freedom News Place of publication: Richmond, Calif. Publisher: Freedom News, 1969-1974 (Box 157)
  - Freedom Reader Place of publication: Flint, Mich. Publisher: Freedom Reader Publications, 1971 (Box 157)
  - Freedom Socialist Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Freedom Socialist Party, 1976-current (Box 157-158)
  - Freeway Place of publication: Duluth, Minn. (Box 157)
  - The Freeworld Times Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: The Murian Foundation for Criminal Justice, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 341)
  - Freie arbeiter stimme Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Free Voice of Labor Association, 1972-1977 (Box 158A)
  - Frente libertario Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Frente Libertario, 1975-1977 (Box 157)
  - Friars' Epistle Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York American, 1917 (Box 512)
  - Friday Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Friday, Inc., 1940-1941 (Box 488)
  - Friends Place of publication: London, England (Box 158A)
  - Friendshipment Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Friendshipment, 1978 (Box 152)
  - From the Horse's Mouth Place of publication: Pittsburgh, Pa. Publisher: Concerned Rank and File Teamsters (CRAFT), 1975 (Box 501)
  - The Front Place of publication: Tallahassee, Fla. Publisher: People's Revolutionary News Service, nd-1972 (Box 38)
  - Front libertaire Place of publication: Paris, France, 1972-1976 (Box 28)
  - Frontline Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Line of March Publications, 1972-1990 (Box 159-160)
  - Frontlines Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: C. Petroni, 2002-2004 (Box 160)
  - Frontpage Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, American Newspaper Guild, CIO, 1947-2000 (Box 173)
  - Full Moon Place of publication: Amherst, Mass., nd (Box 477)
  - Fur Age Weekly Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Fur Vogue Publishing Co., 1990 (Box 160)
  - Furriers Joint Council Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Furriers Joint Council of New York, 1951 (Box 160)
  - Furriers Joint Council Reporter, 1958-1975 (Box 160)
  - FUSA Advocate Place of publication: Jacksonville, Fla. Publisher: Florida United Service Association, 1974 (Box 487)
  - Futuro Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: La Delegacion Del FORDC de Nueva York, 1962 (Box 28)
- G
  - La Gaceta chibcha Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969-1970 (Box 223)
  - La Gaceta de Cuba Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Unión de Escritores y Artistas de Cuba, 1965 (Box 165)
  - El Gallo Place of publication: Denver, Colo. Publisher: El GAllo News, 1972 (Box 174)
  - The Garden Place of publication: Binghamton, N.Y., 1988 (Box 165)
  - The Garment Worker Place of publication: England Publisher: National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1976 (Box 165)
  - The Garment Worker Place of publication: Harrisburg, Pa. Publisher: Locals 108, 196 and 197, Northeast Dept., International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, 1963-1975 (Box 167)
  - The Garment Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Garment Workers of America, 1963-1980 (Box 500)
  - La Gauche Place of publication: Belgium, 1967-1968 (Box 435)
  - Gay Community News Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: GCN, 1982 (Box 171)
  - The Gay Liberator Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Pansy Press (Box 165)
  - Gay Sunshine Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Winston Leyland, 1972-1976 (Box 165)
  - GCEOC - CIO News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, CIO, 1953 (Box 171)
  - Genesis 2 Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Genesis 2, 1985 (Box 174)
  - Gente de Aztlán Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: ASUCLA Communications Board, 1973 (Box 174)
  - Georgia Straight Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Georgia Straight Pub., 1971-1973 (Box 166)
  - German American Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: German American Inc., 1944-1963 (Box 167-168)
  - Getting Together Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: I Wor Kuen, 1970-1978 (Box 170)
  - GI News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: NOSCAM-Chicago, 1974-1975 (Box 163)
  - GI Press Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1970-1971 (Box 163)
  - Gidra Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Gidra, Inc., 1970 (Box 31)
  - Gimme Shelter Place of publication: Ironbound, Publisher: 108, 1971 (Box 171)
  - Gold Coast Free Press Place of publication: Coconut Grove, Fla. Publisher: Gold Coast Free Press, Inc., 1971 (Box 171)
  - Gold Flower Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: The Gold Flower Collective, 1971-1979 (Box 477)
  - Goob Yeak Gergibal Place of publication: East Lansing, Mich., nd (Box 171)
  - Good Times Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1969-1972 (Box 171)
  - Goodbye to All That Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1970-1971 (Box 171)